Hi, I'm Shachi.
There are three of us, Kiya-san's friend, Nabe.
And
Eel Salt Chashu Noodle
Two of these gift ramen cats
I'd like to eat them!
Yay!
I've already got them as soon as possible
While eating them...
I'd like to talk about something else.
I have prepared it for you this time.
Sue!
So cute!
Let me explain... who is Sue?
Surakiya's signature girl.
Ramen Soup!
It's a reward recording, where we pull a theme from this box over here and try to eat delicious food while chatting with each other.
Thank you very much.
Well, let's open it first, shall we?
Open it!
It's ready to be finished,
There's a kimchi nabe waiting for you there.
Me?
I'll go.
Yum! Looks delicious!
Yum!
Looks good!
It's so good!
It smells so good.
Beautiful color. Beautiful coloring.
Nice... lots of vegetables.
Great!
Looks delicious.
I'll make a casserole.
A pot.
Thank you.
Looks delicious.
Tastes like meat.
Yes, it does
Thank you.
Okay, please.
I think they have udon noodles.
Let's eat a lot.
Okay, then.
Nabe and over here is chashu pork.
Umashio chashu pork.
I knew it! It's just a ding-dong!
That's right.
All you have to do is put it in the zipper.
Let me explain.
What is the source of Gifu Tamenkanju Umashio Chashu?
It's a special seasoning that allows you to make chashu pork with the flavor of salted malted rice and the richness of garlic in the microwave.
It's a special seasoning that can be made in the microwave.
For ramen soup
Yes, sir.
Then, please clasp your hands together
I did.
Bon appétit! Bon appétit!
Yay!
It was warm!
Yum!
Delicious!
Bon appétit!
Not just spicy.
Not too soft.
Even if you don't like spicy food...
You can enjoy it.
It's got umami.
Umami?
It'll take a while...
There it is.
Where was it? I said umami.
Just eat this one right now.
Oh, no.
Oh, no?
This is bad.
Bon appétit.
Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!
Tasty!
I want some!
Delicious!
I would like to be recorded here regularly!
Delicious
Is it really only cheese?
I want to buy a box!I want to buy a box.
I want to buy a box.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's good.
It's the best.
Let's go to Max's, shall we?
Let's do it.
Okay, then.
This is me.
I'm off for a week.
What do you want to do?
It's fun. It's not every day you get a week off.
When it's in a row.
What do you want to do?
We can do whatever you want.
No restrictions?
I have a lot of money.
Oh, my God.
What should we do?
But travel is always the first thing that comes to mind.
Yeah.
Where do you want to go?
I want to climb Mt Fuji.
Wouldn't it be nice to have a week?
Including vacation.
Fuji.
Fuji.Let's go to Mt.
Fuji first?
Let's go to Mt. Fuji first.
I'm tired.
Fuji express
Fuji Express.
What?
Let's go.
We'll split up.
Mt. Fuji is divided into two.
In the daytime
During the daytime
During sleep
I want to go abroad.
Fuji and go abroad?
Oh, no.
It's been a week.
You're too energetic.
Mt. Fuji.
Fuji, we only need a few days.
Let's go climb some foreign mountains.
Let's go climb somewhere else
In our lyrics
Chomolungma
Chomolungma in our lyrics
It's the highest form of love.
Wouldn't it be great if we could go private?
But in the meantime...But in the meantime.
I can't get used to being a little lower.
Well, then, Mt. Fuji.
That's the math.
Have you climbed Diamond Head?
I have.
How many meters?
About a thousand.
Not that many.
Did you climb that? It's up, it's up, it's up.
We're climbing.
We've done it. We've done it.
Maybe we can climb a mountain with fiber.
Yeah, sure.
I'm scared.
What kind of meters?
232, sir.
That's low.
That's why I don't remember much.
It was a hike, not a climb.
Oh, I see. Is it 200?
It's more like a mountain. I don't even remember it being that strenuous.
Yes, it was.
It was a little more like climbing a mountain.
It's like you get a little emotional afterwards.
Like a sense of accomplishment.
That's for sure.
The top mountain in Aichi Prefecture
Let's start from Mt. Chausei.
About 1500 About 1,500.
Right.
But that's because that's the price.
That's great.
Let's draw another one.
Do you want to give him some tea next time?
Yes, ma'am.
What is it?
What movies, cartoons and dramas have you seen recently?
Yeah.
Everyone's been watching a lot lately.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You watch it every day.
I'm busy.
You see it every day.
Busy.
But, Spring, I imagine you watch it all the time when you're on the move.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's great. What are you looking at? The book series.
I've been watching most of it.
What are you doing? I don't know. It's pretty annoying. Tell me, tell me.
What neighborhood? What are you doing?
Drama.
Let's see, B.
Prurion Games, 1840.
Best Student, Best Teacher.
What else can I say?
King of Execution
I have to use the video feature like in the old days.You have to use the video feature like in the old days.
You watch it on the move.
The beautiful version is funny, too.
What's it about?
I have no idea.
It's hard to explain.
What's it about?
There's a lot of people doing a lot of thinking about it.
There's a lot of discussion going on right now.
I've never said anything about it.
Suspense?
There's no suspense.
In the very first episode.
There's a guy named Nogi, played by Mr. Sakai.
Nogi works for a company in a bank.
He's supposed to send 100,000 yen to a company overseas.
"We'll send 100,000 yen to an overseas company.
But I got one digit wrong.
It was supposed to be about 1 million yen.
But there was a lot of excitement in the company.
What's going on? What's going on? Like, "What's wrong?
I said...
It wasn't a million dollars.
I think it was like 10 billion dollars.
It's a lot smaller than that. It's 100,000 yen.
Let me explain.
Biban is a drama that starts when a client is supposed to transfer 1.4 billion yen to a business partner.
But 14 billion yen was transferred by supplementary remittance.
By the way, Akimoto's talking about 10 billion dollars.
That's about 1.5 trillion Japanese yen.That's about 1.5 trillion Japanese yen.
preview of the next installment
Mr. Sario Abe's
I can go to Mr. Sarasaburo Abe again.
You can go to Mr. Sarabo Abe in Japan.
The one with Mr. Sarabo Abe is my favorite.
He's my favorite.
I heard there was one before that.
When Mr. Abe came out...
You didn't have that one in your story.
Dr. Abe.
I made a mistake.
Now that you mention it, I'm pretty sure you're mistaken about the candy.
Wrong.
You're Sato-san, right?
I've been watching the drama.
I'm looking forward to another week.
It's fun to have a period like that.
It's super fun.
I want to see it so bad.
I'm waiting for it to come out on subs.
The silent one.
Is it on?
Is it?
We're showing all the episodes for free.
All free episodes?
I'll watch the whole thing until all the episodes are free.
It's a spin-off or something.
I'm rewatching it.
I want to see it so bad.I really, really want to see it.
How much are you watching?
When are you watching?
But, you know, you're out by the hall.
They're out.
When are you watching it?
When you're on the road, when you're not sleeping.
When you're in the hall, when you're on the road, do you ever watch the half-pace?
Half-paced tea?
Thank you for your time.
So, you've got your baby carriage, too.
You know what I mean, don't you?
I know the baby carriage.
Do you want to keep the baby carriage?
I don't know. I don't know. I have a baby carriage.
What? Oh, the pie thing.
Yeah, that's right.
I didn't take the baggy.
I don't think anybody likes you.
They like me now.
But, like, I'm going to buy another baby carriage.
Pretty much.
I don't know.
He's a nice guy
He's a good guy, but
It's a baby carriage, too.
So if you knew the other side...
If you know this side of him, you might understand him better.
I'm going to buy more Nao.
I've been a little busy, haven't I? I'm starting to get a little worked up.
You're pretty cute and lovable.
You know, I think I'm gonna be the pirate king.
I think you're gonna be the pirate king.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Is that what Akimoto-sensei thinks?
Akimoto-sensei thinks that you're a baby carriage.
What? Not Luffy?
What is Luffy?
Can't you be Luffy? The Pirate King.
I think he'll turn it down.
You think so?
That's true.
It's just my imagination.
Baby carriage's kind of hot.
That's the movie version.
That's the movie version, right?
Maybe not.
If it's a baby carriage, I might answer.
Poppo, I wish you'd go on YouTube by yourself.
There are so many of them.
There are so many.
What's the right answer?
Doropizo, right?
Poppo tells you so much?
The manager keeps looking at me.
I think it'd be great. I think it would definitely be a good idea to do it.
I think it's definitely a good idea to do it, because a lot of people are doing it.
Various people are doing it.
Popopo-chan's opinion
I'm not saying "Popopo-chan did it".
I'll go to the standpoint of "But, this is what I want".
Yes, yes, refute it.
LOL!
Let's go next time.
It was a very slow video, but I enjoyed it.
Yes, this hot pot and chashu look delicious today!
If you enjoyed the video, please leave a comment and click the "Good" button!
Also, please subscribe to our channel!
Next time, we'll be looking at Honoka's thoughts on One Piece!
That's all for SixTONES!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel.